Deck.create(name: "New York Geography")

Card.create(question:"What is the name of the main international airport at New York?",answer:"JFK" ,deck_id: 1)
Card.create(question:"New York's financial center is",answer:"Wall Street" ,deck_id: 1)
Card.create(question:"Name the famous New York City building whose construction was completed in 1931.",answer:"Empire State Building" ,deck_id: 1)
Card.create(question:"Where in New York is the advertising industry primarily located?",answer:"Madison Avenue" ,deck_id: 1)
# Card.create(question:"What is the red granite obelisk in Central Park of New York called?",answer:"Cleopatra's Needle" ,deck_id: 1)
# Card.create(question:"How many boroughs is New York made up of?",answer:"5" ,deck_id: 1)
# Card.create(question:"Which of New York's boroughs is the largest in size?",answer:"Queens" ,deck_id: 1)
# Card.create(question:"Which of New York's boroughs is the smallest in size? ",answer:"Manhattan" ,deck_id: 1)
# Card.create(question:"Which New York borough was known as the borough of Richmond until 1975?",answer:"Staten Island" ,deck_id: 1)
# Card.create(question:"Which of New York's boroughs is the most populated?",answer:"Brooklyn" ,deck_id: 1)
# Card.create(question:"About how many islands does New York City consist of?",answer:"50" ,deck_id: 1)
# Card.create(question:"What is the official residence of the Mayor of New York called?",answer:"Gracie Mansion" ,deck_id: 1)
# Card.create(question:"Name one of the world's largest wildlife conservation parks located in New York.",answer:"The Bronx Zoo" ,deck_id: 1)
# Card.create(question:"Where do the Yankees play their professional baseball games in New York?",answer:"Yankee Stadium" ,deck_id: 1)
# Card.create(question:"Where do the Mets play their professional baseball games in New York?",answer:"Shea Stadium" ,deck_id: 1)

Deck.create(name: "California Trivia")

Card.create(question:"What is the capital of California?", answer: "Sacramento", deck_id: 2)
Card.create(question:"What state borders California to the north?", answer: "Oregon", deck_id: 2)
Card.create(question:"What is the largest city in California?", answer: "Los Angeles", deck_id: 2)
Card.create(question:"Who is the current govenor of California?", answer: "Jerry Brown", deck_id: 2)

